izzygames.com 2018-06-29

# Imprint - Game - Play Online For Free - Download

* * *

**Imprint**

 **Branch Office:**  
Feig Ltd.  
Sülte 10  
37520 Osterode  
0175-4014422

 **Mail:**  

 **Register:**  
Company No. 8142686  
Reg. in England & Wales  
Amtsgericht Göttingen  
HRB 201916

 **VAT-ID:**  
DE284099621

 **TAX-ID:**  
29/203/00525

 **Director:**  
Marcel Feig

 **Head Office:**  
69 Great Hampton Street  
B18 6EW Birmingham  
West Midlands  
United Kingdom

 **Privacy Policy**

 **What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

 **What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

\- To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

\- To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

 **How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

**Do we use cookies?**  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

 _Local Shared Objects (Flash Cookies)_  
The website izzygames.com may use Adobe Flash Player to provide game and video content. Local Shared Objects (commonly known as Flash Cookies) may be used to save your in-game stats in a flash game or other user related info's. Flash Cookies are similar to cookies, however they are managed differently. _How to disable Flash Cookies_  
Information on how to disable and delete Flash Cookies is provided on the Adobe website at <http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/security>

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.   
This policy was last modified on 02.08.2012

 **Contacting Us**  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

Feig Ltd.  
Suelte 10  
Osterode, Niedersachsen 37520  
Germany  
webmaster@spiele-umsonst.de

 **Disclaimer for Google-Analytics**  
This website uses Google Analytics, a website analyst software of Google Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses so called “Cookies". These are text files which are stored locally on your computer and make it possible to track the usage of this website. The generated information (including IP-Address) will be forwarded to a server of Google in the United States and stored there locally. Google will use this information to analyze the usage of this page in order to generate reports about the activity of website visitors for the owners of this website and also to show related activity and services of this site. Furthermore Google will transmit this information to third parties in case it is requested by law or to affiliated partners of Google. Google will never connect your IP-Address with any related data. You can also block the installation of Google cookies manually/automatically through your browser software. Through the visit of this website you agree to the usage of the above mentioned data/purpose with the above mentioned methods.

To Opt-Out use this link [http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)

For more Privacy Policy of Google look here <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

Note: This website uses IP anonymization.

 **Disclaimer for Facebook (Facebook Social Plug-in)**  
Our website uses so called Social Plugins („Plugins) of the social network facebook.com, which is operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA (“Facebook”). The plugins are identifiable by one of the Facebook logos (white “f” on a blue background or a “thump-up” sign) or are identified by the phrase “Facebook Social Plugin”. The list and the look of Facebook Social Plugins can be found here: developers.facebook.com/plugins. Purpose and detail of the data assessment and the further use and analysis of the Data through Facebook and your thus related personal rights and control functions to protect your private data can be found in the data disclaimer of Facebook: www.facebook.com/policy.php. If you are a member of Facebook and do not want Facebook to collect your data via our website and stores it in relationship to your Facebook member account, you will need to log out of Facebook prior to the visit of our website and you may also have to delete any related cookies stored locally by Facebook. Furthermore it is possible to block the data generation of Facebook Plug-ins by using browser add-ons such as "Facebook Blocker"

To download the Facebook Blocker look here <http://webgraph.com/resources/facebookblocker/>

For more Privacy Policy of Facebook look here <http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/>

**Disclaimer for Google+ (Google)-Plus-Plugins**  
Our website uses the "+1" plugin provided by the social network Google Plus, operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, United States ("Google"). The plugin is labeled with the Google +1 logo on a white or colored background. When you visit a page of our website that contains a social plugin, your browser establishes a direct connection to Google servers. Google directly transfers the "+1" plugin content to your browser which embeds the latter into the website. While we therefore have no influence on the extent of data gathered by the plugin, we inform you that your IP address is detected. For information on the purpose and scope of data collection and processing by Google, as well as your rights in this respect and settings options for protecting your privacy, please visit Google’s "+1" privacy policy. If you are a Google Plus member and do not want Google to connect the data concerning your visit to our website with your member data already stored by Google, please log off Google before entering our website.

For more Privacy Policy look here <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>
